Guide to the Kulchur Foundation records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series VI: Publications, 1961-1993
  - Periodicals
    - Books
      - Tear to Open, Bob Holman (Box 53)
      - Derviche/Le Robert Bernard Heidsieck (Box 53)
      - Silver Flower Coo, Charles Henri Ford (Box 53)
      - Manhattan Carnival, Frederick Feirstein (Box 53)
      - Agnes & Sally, Lewis Warsh (Box 53)
      - Code Poems, Hannah Weiner (Box 53)
      - The Sound of One Mind Thinking, Eugene Schwartz (Box 53)
      - Rude Awakenings, Bob Rosenthal (Box 53)
      - The Luis Armed Story, Tom Veitch (Box 53)
      - The Helen Review (Box 53)
      - Utopia, Bernadette Mayer (Box 53)
      - Sun and Moon, 1980 (Box 53)
      - The Quarterly 43, 1978 (Box 53)
      - The Diaries of Judith Malina, Judith Malina (Box 53)
      - Myths, Andy Warhol (Box 53)
      - Journal of a Hermit, Janine Pommey Vega (Box 53)
      - Staves Calends legends, Thomas Meyer